(Raj:)I'm the friend you call
when you have no other options.
(Raj:)If we were the Justice League,
I'd be Aquaman.
(Howard:)I wish you were Aquaman.
(Howard:)Then I could send you to scoop my mom
out of the old-lady tank.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me, I'm thirsty...
(Sheldon:)...so I'm going to go to the refrigerator
and get myself a refreshing beverage.
(Leonard:)You know what?
I'll just spend the evening alone.
What? Suddenly, I'm not good enough
for you?
[SIGHS]
(Sheldon:)I do so love beverages.
(Sheldon:)Now I think
I'll take my after-dinner walk.
(Leonard:)Since when do you take
after-dinner walks?
(Howard:)Since when do you take walks?
(Sheldon:)I read a study online that walking
after a meal not only aids in digestion...
(Sheldon:)...but increases serotonin.
(Sheldon:)If there's one thing I like more than a
refreshing beverage, it's serotonin. Bye.